jobsbotswana.info 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Jobs Botswana | Jobs in Botswana - Accounting and Finance jobs in Botswana

This privacy policy applies to [https://www.jobsbotswana.info](https://www.jobsbotswana.info/) owned and operated by Empire Solutions PBC. (“Jobs Botswana”). This privacy policy describes how Empire Solutions PBC. collects and uses the personal information you provide on our website: [https://www.jobsbotswana.info.](https://www.jobsbotswana.info./)

1\. Introduction

The Company(s) referred to herein as “Jobs Botswana” refers to Empire Solutions and any of its divisions, including but not limited to www.jobsbotswana.info

2\. Information Collection & Use

Jobs Botswana is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Jobs Botswana collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

3\. Job Seeker Registration

In order to use the functionality of this website, a user must first complete the two step registration form. During registration a user is required to provide all the information needed to complete the CV in the system.

We request the following information in our CV form:

• Full Name

• Date of Birth

• ID Number

• Affirmative Action Job Seeker (African/Coloured/Indian/Disabled/Female)

• Phone Number

• Additional Phone Number (optional)

• Email Address

• Location

• Languages

• Education Details

• Employment History

• Skills

• Associations

• Achievements

• My Next Job

• Availability

• Searchability

This information is used for the Online Recruitment process and this includes sending Job Seeker CVs to a Recruiter for the purpose of a Job Seekers job application process where such CV data may then be stored by the Recruiter for future recruitment consideration. A Recruiter may also make contact with a Job Seeker for recruitment opportunities as a result of a CV search conducted by the Recruiter on searchable CVs on the Jobs Botswana database. If we have trouble processing a request, the contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

This information can be shared on search engine to allow easy searchability of recruiters and job seekers profile. By creating an account with Jobs Botswana a user consents to search engine indexing their profile.

4\. Recruiter Registration

Information that is collected from subscribing Recruiters will be used to contact the Recruiter about the services for which they have expressed interest. If Recruiters want to change their information their company supervisor has access to do this using the Supervisor Tools functionality.

This information is used for the Online Recruitment process and this includes sending Job Seeker CVs to a Recruiter for the purpose of a Job Seekers job application process where such CV data may then be stored by the Recruiter for future recruitment consideration. A Recruiter may also make contact with a Job Seeker for recruitment opportunities as a result of a CV search conducted by the Recruiter on searchable CVs on the Jobs Botswana database. If we have trouble processing a request, the contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

5\. Cookies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Jobs Botswana and our partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analysing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these Companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for tracking usage behaviour, recognise repeat users, manage user access and track user settings. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

6\. Log Files

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

7\. Sharing

We sometimes share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to personally identifiable information. We also partner with third parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names or other information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. We will not voluntarily disclose any information about individual users to third parties, except as described in this privacy statement, or to comply with applicable laws or valid legal process, or to protect the rights or property of Jobs Botswana and its partner sites.

Jobs Botswana maintains relationships with outside service providers for some of the services offered through our site, for example Ecocash and Telecash.

**Google can index the Job Seeker Profile and Recruiters profile. When you create you create your profile you are consenting to this when you tick the Agree button.**

The information these providers make available may be presented in a “framed” format, where the Jobs Botswana border will surround the pages served by the service provider, or where pages have the look and feel of Jobs Botswana. In either case, the service provider is prominently identified. Please be aware that any information you provide on those framed pages is provided directly to those service providers and is subject to their security and privacy policies. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these outside service providers because their privacy practices may differ from ours.

8\. Legal Disclaimer

We may also disclose your personal information:

• as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process

• when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,

• if Jobs Botswana is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,

• to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

9\. Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Jobs Botswana is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected on pages of this site.

10\. Communications

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify their username and password. Users also have the choice to subscribe to our newsletter. A user can unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time from both our site and the newsletter itself.

Jobs Botswana may use your information to contact you about promotions and services. You are entitled, at any stage, to opt out of this service, by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” option on the email correspondence. This will redirect you to the unsubscribe page where you will be able to unsubscribe from the communication you received.

From time to time we may send out critical service announcements. Users are not able to unsubscribe from critical service announcements, which contain important information about the service.

11\. Security and Data Storage

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information online. When asked to enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number), the information is encrypted and is protected via secure sockets layer (SSL) encryption technology.

We also do everything in our power to protect user information offline. Access to all of our users’ information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our Client Service Team) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure, access controlled environment. If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as their email address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal details provided to us. This can be done from the user’s CV page or by emailing our Client Service Team at info@jobsbotswana.info.

12\. Access and Choice

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, ask to have it removed from a public forum, directory or testimonial on our site or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at  **info@jobsbotswana.info.**  We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

13\. Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

14\. Choice/Opt Out

Users who no longer wish to allow their CV to be searchable by our subscribers may opt out of this facility by going to their CV page, and select to be non-searchable. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may opt out of receiving it by going to their settings page and select to not receive newsletters.

15\. Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage prior to the change becoming effective.
